wesbanco.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy

Our customers’ confidence in our ability to provide premier financial services while preserving the integrity of their personal information is the cornerstone of WesBanco’s success and reputation. As technology enhances our ability to deliver our services in new and innovative ways, we understand your concerns of how this development may impact your personal privacy. We recognize our responsibility not only to protect the financial assets entrusted to us, but also to respect the privacy expectations of our customers. Our commitment to that responsibility is outlined in our adoption of the following privacy principles: 

**Recognition of a Customer's Expectation of Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. We recognize your personal interest in understanding how we do business - in understanding how we will collect, retain, and use the personal information we request from you. By publishing this privacy policy, we hope to address those concerns and instill confidence in our existing and potential customers that WesBanco has sufficient standards and security measures in place to prevent the misuse of any personal information provided to us. We will continually re-evaluate these standards to ensure your privacy is respected. We welcome your questions and comments. 

Please write to us at: WesBanco, Attn: Bank Operations , 1 Bank Plaza, Wheeling, WV 26003,   
or e-mail us using the following link. [custserv@wesbanco.com](mailto:custserv@wesbanco.com)

**What Information We Collect**

We may collect “nonpublic personal information” about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other loan and account forms, such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income;  
.
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others, such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage; and  
.
  * Information we receive from credit reporting agencies, such as your creditworthiness and credit history. 

“Nonpublic personal information” is nonpublic information about you that we obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. For example, nonpublic personal information includes information regarding your account balance, payment history, and overdraft history. 

**What Information We Disclose**

We are permitted under law to share information about our experiences or transactions with you or your account (such as your account balance and your payment history with us) with companies related to us by common control or ownership (“affiliates”). 

We also are permitted under law to disclose nonpublic personal information about you to “nonaffiliated third parties” (i.e., third parties that are not members of our corporate family) in certain circumstances. For example, we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to such third parties to assist us in servicing your loan or account with us; to government entities in response to subpoenas; and to credit bureaus. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to any other third parties, except as permitted by law. 

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. 

Otherwise, we do not share customer information with outside companies for purposes of selling their products and services to you. We do not sell “customer lists” to outside companies. 

To read more about the specific information collected and retained through our website, www.wesbanco.com, and online banking service, WesBancoNet, please access the WesBanco Internet Banking Security Statement. 

**Maintenance of Accurate Information**

WesBanco is committed to maintaining the integrity of your financial information. We have developed procedures to ensure our customer records are accurate, current, and complete in accordance with reasonable commercial standards. Our employees are prepared to respond to your requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner. You may direct such requests to: WesBanco, Attn: Bank Operations, 1 Bank Plaza, Wheeling, WV, 26003, or to the address and telephone number provided on your monthly statement. Additionally, when you open certain types of accounts with us, we will provide you with disclosures outlining specific procedures for you to follow should you find an error or unauthorized transaction on your account. These disclosures are also available through our online banking service, WesBancoNet.

**Limiting Employee Access to Information**

As stated previously, WesBanco will only use personal customer information for legitimate business purposes. This extends to limiting your personally identifiable information to those WesBanco employees with a business reason to know such information about you. We educate our employees on the importance of customer privacy. We have outlined our standards for employee confidentiality in our corporate Personnel Policies and Procedure Manual provided to each employee. Breaches of our confidentiality principles are grounds for disciplinary action against the employee. 

**Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures**

WesBanco continually maintains and updates appropriate security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information. We are committed to utilizing the newest technologies to enhance these standards and to keep the information you provide to us secure and confidential. All of our operational and data processing systems are in a secure environment that protects your account information from being accessed by third parties. 

To read more about the security of information you provide to us through our website, www.wesbanco.com and through our online banking service, WesBancoNet, please access the WesBanco Internet Banking Security Statement. 

**Children Visiting Our Web Site**

Our web site and online banking services are designed to provide information and deliver products and services to current and prospective customers of WesBanco. We anticipate the users of our electronic banking options to be adults, and we limit access to WesBancoNet to account holders over the age of sixteen. Our web site may be viewed by the general public and could be accessed by a child, although we are confident that none of the information available would be considered objectionable. We will not knowingly solicit or gather personal identifying information from a child. Should a child e-mail us from our web site to ask a question or to request product or service information, and we have knowledge that the request was from a child under the age of thirteen, the child’s e-mail address would be retained only for the time period and purpose of responding to the request. 

Parents may exercise control over which areas of the Internet their children access by utilizing the variety of software packages and computer technologies currently available for that purpose. 

**Our Commitment to your Privacy -  
Disclosure of Privacy Principles to Customers**

WesBanco is committed to protecting the confidentiality of the personal information you share with us and in keeping you informed of the privacy and security principles we adopt to do so. You can expect this commitment to extend equally whether you visit us in person, over the telephone, or through our website or online banking service. 

This privacy policy applies to personal information gathered and used in your covered transactions with WesBanco companies that are for personal, family, or household purposes, as required by the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and any implementing regulation. These companies include WesBanco Bank, Inc., WesBanco Trust and Investment Services, WesBanco Securities, Inc., WesBanco Insurance Services, and Hometown Finance Company. This policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice given to you unless otherwise required by law or regulation. If any change would result in you having the right to “opt out” of information sharing as provided for in any law or regulation, i.e., to direct us not to share your information, you would be given a reasonable time to exercise this right prior to the revised policy becoming effective. 

If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice.
